hi this is a quick demo showing you the
嗨，这是一个快速演示，向您展示了
support we have in SDS for for editing
支持我们在SDS中进行编辑
spring boot properties what you see here
spring boot属性你在这里看到的
on the screen is an application
屏幕上是一个应用程序
properties file and it's open in our
属性文件，它在我们的文件中打开
properties editor we have two editors
属性编辑器我们有两个编辑器
for this we have one that works with the
为此，我们有一个与
properties file format and one that
属性文件格式以及
works with the mo file format
适用于mo文件格式
I'd rather demo you the mo file format
我想给你演示一下mo文件格式
because it's more interesting so first
因为它更有趣，所以首先
thing I'm gonna do is actually convert
我要做的事情实际上是convert依
this file into a mo file so we just do
将此文件转换为mo文件，这样我们就可以
that by right click on this properties
通过右键单击此属性
file and select convert properties to ml
文件，然后选择将属性转换为ml
from the menu and then it's gonna show
从菜单上，然后将显示
you what it's gonna do so it's going to
你会怎么做，它将
transform this into this here if you
如果你把这个变成这个
like what you see all you have to do is
就像你看到的，你要做的就是
click OK and it's gonna apply those
单击确定，它将应用那些
changes to the workspace and there we go
改变工作区，然后我们去
now we have the same file but now in the
现在我们有相同的文件，但是现在在
mo format so let's have a quick tour of
mo格式，让我们快速浏览
the features of the ml editor the first
ml编辑器的功能第一个
thing I want to show is that if you
我想展示的是，如果你
hover over these properties you get the
将鼠标悬停在这些属性上，您将
documentation for the properties which
属性文件
is nice so you can just hover over any
很好，所以您可以将鼠标悬停在任何
of these properties and see what they
这些属性，看看他们有什么
are for what they mean the second thing
代表第二件事
that it does is it checks the structure
它所做的是检查结构
of your file so for example here you see
文件的内容，例如，在这里您可以看到
that Eureka client enabled is supposed
应该启用了Eureka客户端
to be a boolean if I type something here
如果我在这里输入一些内容，将成为布尔值
that's not a boolean it will complain
那不是布尔值，它会抱怨
about that and tell you that's not what
关于这个，告诉你那不是什么
you expect here it should be a boolean
您期望这里应该是布尔值
so make it a boolean again similarly if
因此，如果再次将其设为布尔值，
I change this for example to something
我将其更改为例如
that's not a number the same kind of
这不是同一类型的数字
thing happens if I make it title in a
如果我将标题设为
name it will tell you this name is not
名字会告诉你这个名字不是
as expected okay so we also have
正如预期的那样，所以我们也有
completions of course so if I type
当然完成，所以如果我输入
something here like happening and then
这里发生的事情然后
the completion will suggest similar
完成将表明类似
things over enzyme spring application
酶春季应用的事情
name or Eureka instance app names are
名称或Eureka实例应用名称是
going to think that I'm similar to what
会认为我与
I typed and women circle for us in the
我输入了字母，妇女在
right what's very nice about this editor
对，这个编辑器有什么好处
is that it's smart enough to insert
它足够聪明地插入
stuff in the right place as well so if I
东西也放在正确的地方，如果我
for example want to add some
例如要添加一些
availability zones to my Eureka client
我的尤里卡客户的可用区
then I can just select this property and
然后我可以选择该属性
it jumps
它跳
to the place where the other properties
到其他属性的地方
are for Eureka client inserted in that
用于插入其中的Eureka客户
place so that's kind of the features of
的地方，这样的特点
the editor that I wanted to demo the
我想演示的编辑器
next thing I want to show you is how you
接下来我想告诉你的是你如何
can also make this work with your own
也可以自己制作
properties all of these are just
所有这些都是
property is defined by spring boot you
属性是由spring boot定义的
can also make it work with user-defined
也可以使其与用户定义的一起使用
properties
属性
so I'm did that here I created a class
所以我在这里做了一个课
to define some properties the class is
定义类的一些属性
called welcome properties and I just
叫做欢迎财产，我只是
have to annotate that with an ad
必须用广告来注释
configuration properties annotation and
配置属性注释和
provide a prefix now all the things that
现在提供所有内容的前缀
I define in here all the bean properties
我在这里定义所有的bean属性
like welcomed of messages and welcome
喜欢欢迎留言和欢迎
dot enable will be the properties that
点启用将是
I'm defining here there is a little
我在这里定义有一点
yellow marker here so let's hover over
黄色标记在这里，让我们将鼠标悬停
that what it's telling us is that we
告诉我们的是
should add something to our pom file to
应该将一些东西添加到我们的pom文件中
make this work nicely so without that
使这项工作很好，所以没有那个
there will be no metadata for these
这些将没有元数据
properties and editor won't know that
属性和编辑器不会知道
they exists so let's add this convert
他们存在，所以让我们添加这个转换
this to our pom all we have to do is
这对我们的pom我们要做的就是
accept this little quick fix here which
在这里接受这个小小的快速修复
is going to do that for us so the quick
将为我们做到这一点，所以快速
fix added something our upon let's do a
修复添加了一些我们可以做的
quick look at that just to see what it
快速看一下，只是看看它是什么
did so I'm just gonna do here compare
做到了，所以我只是在这里做比较
with AD revision and what you can see is
使用AD修订版，您可以看到的是
it added the configuration processor to
它添加了配置处理器
my palm and that's what's gonna make the
我的手掌，这将使
metadata automatically appear in the
元数据自动出现在
class man so now that we have this
班级的人，所以现在我们有了这个
working when we what we did here this
当我们在这里做什么时工作
should all work so let's try it and if I
应该都可以工作，所以让我们尝试一下，如果我
say welcome to enable and again same
说欢迎启用，然后再说一次
support as we have for all the other
像其他人一样支持
good properties it's expecting a boolean
好的属性，期望布尔值
here is not a string so that's something
这不是字符串，所以
like this okay so the last thing I want
像这样好吧，我想要的最后一件事
to show you is that we also have an
告诉你，我们也有一个
editor like this in vyas Visual Studio
在vyas Visual Studio中像这样的编辑器
code so let me open visuals to real
代码，所以让我打开真实的视觉效果
quick and just show you that it works
快速并向您展示它的工作原理
there as well so if you see here hover
还有，所以如果你在这里看到悬停
over service URL you get the
通过服务URL，您将获得
documentation if you make a typo you get
文档，如果您输入错误，您将得到
a little squiggly warning and we have
有点弯曲的警告，我们有
also got nice content assist here
在这里也有很好的内容帮助
so let's see what we can do like for
让我们来看看我们可以做什么
example Jack's on Jack so big for Monty
例如杰克在杰克身上对蒙蒂如此重要
Aviara and this is kind of where I want
Aviara，这是我想要的地方
to end my demo I hope you enjoyed it and
结束我的演示，希望您喜欢它，并且
thanks for watching the demo
感谢您观看演示
you
您